



+94 76 260 5123

isurueranga.0@gmail.com

955/4/A, Williyamgopallawa Mawatha, Gatambe, Kandy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/is uru-eranga

https://github.com/isurueranga-98

https://www.ieranga.me

EDUCATION

3rd Year Undergraduate following B.Sc. (Hons) in Information Systems

Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka 2021- Present

G.C.E Advanced Level in Physical Stream Kingswood College, Kandy

SKILLS

Frontend Technologies

- React JS
- Next JS
- Angular
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Redux and Redux Toolkit
- Tailwind CSS
- shaden, MUI

Backend Technologies

- Node JS
- Express JS

Mobile

React Native

Databases

- MongoDB
- MySQL

ISURU ERANGA

Frontend Developer | UI UX Designer | Data Science Enthusiast Information System Undergraduate

ABOUT ME

An enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, and hardworking undergraduate currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science (Honors) degree in Information Systems. Extensive experience as a Frontend Developer and UI/UX Designer, demonstrated through continuous efforts to improve by experimenting with different technologies. Original and innovative solutions are developed while staying up to date with the most recent technology and trends.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

2023 - Present

Frontend Developer (React JS, Next JS, Typescript, Tailwind CSS)

Graphic Designer

May 2023 - Present Remote Graphic Designer at Asiri Trading, Singapore

EXTRA QUALIFICATIONS

Certificates for Web Developing

Completed React Course at Namastedev.com

Completed Frontend System Design Course at Namastedev.com

Completed JavaScript Course at Namastedev.com

Completed Responsive Website: Code with HTML, CSS and JavaScript at Coursers.org

Certificates for Machine Learning

Completed a Data Science with Python course at University of Colombo School of Computing

Completed an Unsupervised Learning, Recommenders, Reinforcement Learning at Coursers.org

Completed an Advanced Learning Algorithms at Coursers.org

Completed a Supervised Machine Learning: Regression and Classification at Coursers.org

Other Languages and Technologies

- C
- Java
- Python

Python Libraries for Machine Learning

- NumPy
- Scikit-learn
- Pandas
- TensorFlow
- Keras
- PyTorch
- Matplotlib

Other Technologies

- Figma
- Adobe Photoshop

API

GraphQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Team work
- Good communication
- Leadership
- Eligibility to accept challenges
- Organizing & Planning
- Decision Making
- Problem Solving

REFERENCES

Ashansa Wijeratne

Lecturer (Probationary)
Department of Software Engineering
Faculty of Computing
Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka
ashansaw@appsc.sab.ac.lk
+94 77 46 17 654

Mr. Sanjeewa Milan

Software Engineer at Amused group sanjeewamj@gmail.com

+94 71 619 1957

Other Certificates

Completed the course by demonstrating theoretical and practical understanding of Python Data Structures at Sololearn

Completed the course by demonstrating theoretical and practical understanding of Python Core at Sololearn

Completed C Programming: Modular Programming and Memory Management at Edx.org

PROJECTS

Classic Teak Furniture - Group (Ongoing)

2024

An e-commerce website for a furniture company featuring an augmented reality (AR) tool allowing customers to virtually place and view furniture products in their own space. This platform facilitates online sales and showcases a diverse range of furniture items, providing an immersive and interactive shopping experience for users.

Technologies | React JS, MongoDB, TypeScript, Redux, Node JS

LabLynx - Group (Ongoing)

2024

A comprehensive web-based system designed for a medical laboratory enabling efficient patient registration, detailed recording of test information, and automated report generation. The system allows reports to be printed or emailed to users and includes advanced data analysis capabilities to predict patterns and trends in medical test results, enhancing diagnostic accuracy and operational efficiency.

Technologies | React JS, MongoDB, TypeScript, Redux, Node JS

NisaBookland - Group (Ongoing)

2024

An e-commerce website designed for a book publication and bookshop company, enabling the seamless online sale and management of books. This platform provides customers with a user-friendly interface to browse, purchase, and track orders, while also offering robust tools for the company to manage inventory, process transactions, and promote new releases and bestsellers.

Technologies | Next JS, MongoDB, React JS, React Native, Node JS, TypeScript

Food Ordering System

2023

An e-commerce website for a pizza ordering service enabling customers to place orders online.

Technologies: - Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB

Hello Green 2023

Web application for non-biodegradable wastes selling and buying.

Technologies: - Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

A member of the IEEE Student Branch

A member of Society of Computer Sciences (SoCS)

A member of University Basketball Team